How well do these lists convey the sense of what these journals are about?


a few instances of output is:

('memory', 'power', 'consumption')
('data', 'structures')
(parallel', 'algorithm')
(hash', 'table')
(distributed', 'memory', 'systems')
('parallel', 'applications')

this says that journal is about parallel computing


Did the same bigram or trigram show up in the list from more than one article?

Yes, similar bigrams and trigrams are shown from various articles
ex:

('parallel', 'applications') and ('parallel', 'algorithm')
('sufﬁx', 'array', 'construction') and ('data', 'array', 'elements')


This program shows some warnings due to different fonts in ACM journal. We can ignore them.
If we copy content of journals to another word file and save it as pdf format, then we dont get any kind of warnings.

